Hello friends, in today's video we will
talk about ICICI GI shares.  Today in this video we will understand
what important level targets,
what important support and resistance
levels can be formed here for the next trading week in ICICI GI share.
Now if we
talk about the trend of the stock here, then
we will see that this stock has been
continuously falling here for a long time and is
seen in a down trend here.
Here we are seeing a continuous lower
lower high pattern in the stock
and at the same time the stock is also
continuously
going down following its trend line.  The stock
took resistance here multiple times,
after which we saw a decline in the stock
and in today's trading session also
we saw a negative closing of 3.16% in the stock here.
That too here
on the same trend line of the stock.  So
from here let us talk about stocks.
If the stock continues to fall from here.
In case of further decline,
we will see the first support of 1737 in the stock here.
If the
stock breaks this, then from here
we have the stock of 618, the stock has
also broken the levels, then from here we can
also see further support levels in the stock,
like here we can
also see support levels up to 1493 in the stock, from there
if there is a
recovery in the stock, in recovery conditions
we will get to see the first resistance of 1895 in the stock,
if the stock breaks this here also, then from
here we have the stock of 1982, if the stock has
also broken the levels here, then from here
we can also see some resistance levels in the stock.
After this, we can also see resistance levels of 2072 and 21200 in the stock here.
So there are some levels in the stock.  There is
no buy sell holding in the rest of the video.
Thanks for watching this video for educational purposes only.